{
    "id": "6324e64d8da34add84bbd91e835ce94b",
    "title": "Conjunctions And Transitional Adverbs",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She was late …………………. we went without her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "so",
                "thus"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7ce378c87fc84ef58841e5674c2895e2"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… I fired at the tiger, he shook my arm.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Until",
                "Because"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8c5409c4d17144ac8e18cf88587a30f5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am glad ………………… tomorrow is a holiday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "so",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5c7391de45e24a69b26a346eb1fc7dd0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was angry …………………. I said nothing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "therefore",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "54e86977c8b540b0a700457bd8f7765d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Vegetables are essential for good health ………………… you must include them in your diet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "since",
                "therefore"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "db4b72276d1846b285fdd1ea1e561bfb"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… you lose your job, what will you do?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Supposing",
                "Supposing if"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5a333e44160140a3acc8ca2b2f6a9b7a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He must be punished ………………… he does not try.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "so long as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8fb50a252bd14d2f86d41e3841b66b3f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is intelligent ………………….. he gets good marks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "as",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9ba2621ff883442ab5139637696e7320"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. he was late he missed the train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "So",
                "Therefore",
                "Because"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "17f8e370655b4d52ba4a184830e07473"
        },
        {
            "question": "There was a big argument about ………………. we should sell our new house.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "weather",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e0d4ee0976984588b1c583a8f30ae3c5"
        }
    ]
}